[
  {

    "question": "What was Loewe's alias while undercover in Sky First Chapter ",
    "choices": ["A. Lorence", "B. Leonhardt", "C. Schwarzritter", "D. Bladelord"],
    "answer": 0
  }, 

  {

    "question": "What are the names of the three members of Kurt Nardin's party that infilterated Ouroboros' base in Sky Second Chapter",
    "choices": ["A. Anelace, Clem, Jill", "B. Grant, Lucy, Agate", "C. Carna, Anelace, Grant", "D. Grant, Aina, Hans"],
    "answer": 2
  },

  {
      "question": "What lead Weissman to join Ouroboros",
      "choices": ["A. The Fall of the Zumerian Empire", "B. The Salt Pale Incident", "C. The Hundred Day War", "D. The Events of Hamel"],
      "answer": 1
  }, 

  {
      "question": "What was Kevin's initial Alias",
      "choices": ["A. Thousand Hand Guardian", "B. Thousand Arms", "C. Heretic Hunter", "D. Soaring Phoneix"],
      "answer": 2
  },

  {
      "question": "Why does Zin stick around Estelle and Joshua in Sky FC",
      "choices": ["A. A favor from Cassius", "B. He needed teammates for the Grancel tournament", "C. Tracking down Walter", "D. Bracer Duties"],
      "answer": 0
  },

  {
      "question": "What's the name of the Organization Richard founds in Sky the 3rd",
      "choices": ["A. Liberl Intelligence Divion", "B. R&A Research", "C. The Guardian Force", "D. Herceles"],
      "answer": 1
  },

  {
      "question": "What's the relation between Duke Dunan to Kole",
      "choices": ["A. Brother", "B. Father", "C. Cousin", "D. Uncle"],
      "answer": 3
  },

  {
      "question": "Which group was Agate apart of before becoming a Bracer",
      "choices": ["A. The Fishermen's Guild", "B. Royal Army of Liberl", "C. The Sky Bandits", "D. The Raven Gang"],
      "answer": 3
  },

  {
      "question": "How many playable characters are in the Sky Triology",
      "choices": ["A. 16", "B. 20", "C. 12", "D. 17"],
      "answer": 1
  },

  {
      "question": "Which of these characters have never had a Stigma",
      "choices": ["A. Kevin Graham", "B. Ein Selnate", "C. Joshua Bright", "D. Ries Argent"],
      "answer": 3
  },

  {
      "question": "What's the name of the ost that plays during the final boss of Trails in the Sky SC",
      "choices": ["A. Hollow Light of the Selaed Land", "B. Fateful Confrontation", "C. Merciless Savior", "D. Whereabouts of Hope"],
      "answer": 2
  }
 ]